Kanye West is banned from the UK and that caused the Wireless Festival to cancel all of Wireless
Festival. And am I mad? No. But also there's a point to be made because two things are happening.
Number one, if you're supporting Kanye West in 2026, all the people that are defending him so
hard, it's the same people that are watching stuff like Fresh and Fit. It's the same people
trying to pull down women at any chance that they can get. Like there's a pattern of the people
in the comments. And if it's a woman, it's a pick me. Like, come on. Kanye didn't get banned because
of the horrible stuff he said about women, black women, black people, none of that. We all know
why he actually got canceled. And because the UK wants to be buddy-buddy with a place committing
actual war crimes, Kanye can't come into the UK. The reasoning behind this is really messed up.
But I am not mad that Kanye isn't performing at Wireless. I'm not mad that Wireless got taken
down and lost all that money because what are you supporting? And I'm not mad that all of his fans,
his loser fans, are in their feelings right now. That's what you get. Sorry, not sorry. Oh well.